Harry LAM

Apply for Junior Frontend Developer

https://www.linkedin.com/in/harry33321
https://harry33321.github.io/

harry33321@gmail.com

+852 6840 2361

A detail-oriented Administration Officer with 2 years of experience to support Accounting, IT, HR and Admin functions in the company. Possess excellent time management skills, ability to multi-tasks and fast learner. Through Generation's course and self-study, I learn some programming skills, such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js etc. For the future, I am looking for an opportunity that lets me expand my programming skills and put my knowledge into practice. Please feel free to visit my portfolio if any interests of my project.

Project Experience

Project Name Task Manager

Project Description A web application with responsive design where user can login to access own

tasks, add new tasks, edit, and delete tasks. It also has a calendar that user can

see the tasks by date.

Technical Skills React.js, Firebase, Bootstrap, MUI, jQuery

Education

Nov 2021 – Feb 2022 Generation Hong Kong

Front-end Web Developer Program

Sep 2017 – Aug 2019 Hong Kong Institute of Vocational Education (Chai Wan)

Higher Diploma of Accountancy

Work Experience

Aug 2019 – Oct 2021 Administration Officer, AccGirl Limited (Innomind Commercial Limited)

- · Handle in-house accounting work and cashier operations daily
- Build various software tools to automate and simplify work process
- Create and maintain databases by Microsoft Access
- Handle basic IT issues for all colleague
- Assist in personnel management and the monthly payroll
- Administrative assistance for all colleague to increase efficiency
- Complete other affairs given by the company, follow the results and report timely

May 2018 – Aug 2019 Server (Part-time), HABITŪ table

role as a cashier, present menus and take orders, brewing coffee and mixing drinks

Jun 2017 – Mar 2018 Cashier (Full-time), Chung Wing Fruits Company Limited

Input data, filed documents, accounting work, acted as a cashier and offered customer service

Technical Skills

Accounting software Sage 50 Peachtree, MYOB, Microsoft Office Accounting

Programming skills HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, API, Bootstrap, Git, GitHub, Firebase, Node.js

Availability Expected Salary

immediate

Negotiable